On behalf of Swat, I request you to
share a comparison of critical illness plans, which are the critical mass
transfer labels, which one should you take, is
it true that you are everyday, who is it, then I
will add after that, before telling, I
would like to tell you that whatever container
plans I will talk about today,
individual videos of all of them are also available
on our channel, you can check them, you can
see them in detail in the video, today we
will compare add difficult issue lemon natural
airplane Aditya Birla retail pack why
made long cricket live Before starting the video,
I would like to clarify to you that there is
no need for Sonam film,
my name is Likh Chikoo Man Usay Panchami
plan and I am associated with the insurance industry for the
last years and I also
bring a lot of electricity so that your
personal life insurance bank
investment jewellery can be simplified and
made only because our company has been advised
that they should be single phase shiny, so comparison
of different strengths and weaknesses
in 9th  Your file is in Jhansi,
chilli in the share market, this is such zinc,
subscribe to the minimum and maximum on Thursday,
like
and
subscribe,
like and
share option, subscribe 30
quote 3 option definition waiting ticket means
after taking the policy, if your first is
not done then you
cannot take its particular screen till the verse, you have a little
waiting period of net of pims, which is president,
so before taking the policy, if you are pregnant,
that fresh juice, due to this, if someone like Kritika
Sengar happens, then you will not be covered for four years,
so all four turns, in this, there is a 4 year audit of
March salary, that is, in glamour politics, there is a
successful period time, survivor
series means your black color and
after that, for how many days it is necessary to survive to
get the manifest for this policy,
so in HBSC, there is a textile oil period,
in such situations, you have to survive for some time,
I have done it in cricket,
survivor series is a small dress, habit, now
till the last and in the root of cervical, fifteen days is a
lubricating in a comprehensive plan, there is
no  The cleaning was done and it will be found out. We will
talk about the free policy medical checkup, which means whether a
medical checkup is required before taking the policy or
not. The
categories will keep changing from time to time
but usually there is no
tax on oil up to 1 lakh and 25 years policy in the categories without any
printed medical insurance, then without
such insurance the policy will start and there is another
category which is applicable in all the policies, the
cuticle policy is
made tasty, if you are salaried then the
12th category of annual income and if the
centerpoint is business then your annual
income of 5th category is eligible for example if
someone has a salary of 10 lakhs then
he is salaried, he can take a policy of up to 1 crore 20 lakhs, and if you delete
here first and
not here then you will not be able to take such a policy,
if you delete and your
income is as per your income then you become 1.5 crores,
we will see these two eligibility criteria
in Max Bupa and Aditya Birla  It will apply that
in both the other places only the Temple of Fertilizer
policy is available Income Tax is also
mentioned If you take this polythene then
you get the rate of section daughter
in all four lines Now let's talk about how many
Aquatic Annual Award and Sa China
HDFC Ergo Critical Illness Cover
you can get out is the real word These
people are in the hints CPI(M) Chairman
Traffic Management Word Aditya Birla
Capital Hus Plan has three clans Basically
here Lal Lal Chunari Lal Lal Mirch 2031
is the obstruction There is a shift in the plant Black crisis
and the word Plant Shift Glass is the
hair-raising word Comprehensive Plan 299
is the word of critical illness So you are attaching this list of all
these in PDF You
can see which one will fit in which
Then the command is what you need
How much comprehensive cover do you want and you
can decide So I will
reach out to you You can send it to me You
can decide whether this cost with balance
suits you  He
subscribes to it for example, I have
taken a premium policy for the cost
and I am clicking on not even as I have taken
premium quality preventive measures on this I have taken
satta lights
because in some clans like tan and party
limit is available sir you are the
manufacturing company of leader and all Apple so I have taken
time to search so if we
take trailers that's why and that Kritika has actually
Supreme yours comes 219 500 yards Prem
including percent GST match is
fixed the premium is 10 lakhs
28 he was stressed Aditya left why take
as I told you these were
or look at the plants the premium account of the shift plant from
64th plan will be less the
plant method will be the highest let's see
their plan which is cost positive net on
search cover from 19838 plants doctors
and nurses plant pre-quarter twelfth
verses
till Monday the poster launch of retailer comprehensive plan
31-05-2018 7 so here we have the
cards  I
saw a comparison in another benefit, then Aditya Birla played
10 with everyone, there are
many launches because of 1981 and if we are
all trees, the penal code is increasing,
so you will see that if we
look at the benefits and when we see the revision, then along with the notifications, the
coverage that we are giving, the
cost that we are getting is
30 pieces, I tell you sir, good cost and Tabrez is
also a lot of actors, I will
tell you that, definitely do the division, see the policy button,
after that decide which plan you should take, you can
watch your individual detail video about this plan, if you want, we will
put it in the description box of our channel first for your
reference, for your convincing, and if you have any question, for example,
garden, ask anything, shade, anything
feet deep, tea, please friend, should I tell you anything,
what have I filled this video with, please
tell me, then at night I felt that the nature of China
and the like this, keep supporting our channel,
a reminder, if till now  If you have
not subscribed to my channel then please
subscribe, problems will give the right
information and right hand and we will meet
soon in the next video, take space and
press
that
[Music] do it
[Music]
Ajay has